http://fciwatermakers.com/privacy-policy/

FCI respects your privacy
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold or rented to any entities or individuals outside of FCI.
Credit card details
FCI will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on FCI.
External Sites
FCI is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows FCI to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information and FCI does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to FCI and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through FCI have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
For any other information contact us.
Clean Water to the World
THE DIFFERENCE IS CLEAR
Contact Us
Or call us at 801.906.8840
Be The First To Know
Sign up for Our Newsletter
CONTACT FCI WATERMAKERS
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
DOWNLOAD SPEC SHEET
Your spec sheet will be sent to the email you provide.
×
ENTER FOR YOUR CHANCE TO WIN!
×
Schedule a Consultation
×
ENTER FOR YOUR CHANCE TO WIN!
×
×
×
×
×
EXPLORE OUR PRODUCTSALL PRODUCTSMARINEMUNICIPALCOMMERCIALCUSTOM FILTRATIONACCESSORIESBENEFITS & FEATURESFCI ADVANTAGEDISTRIBUTIONPARTNERSWARRANTY REGISTRATIONLEARN MOREABOUT USFAQSTESTIMONIALSBLOGCONTACT US
